<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Root><item id="0"><name>Soup of the Day</name><description>Made from the freshest ingredients.</description><price>4.0</price></item><item id="1"><name>Greek Salad</name><description>Feta Cheese tossed with home-made vinaigrette and romaine lettuce.</description><price>10.0</price></item><item id="2"><name>Golden Wedges</name><description>Fluffy in the interior, cripsy in the exterior, these Yukon Gold Potatoes slices imported from Belgian are fried to perfection.</description><price>6.8</price></item><item id="3"><name>Club Sandwich</name><description>Prosciutto crudo from Italy, alongside fresh tomatoes and lettuce with a slice of sharp cheddar are incorporated into a masterpiece with wholemeal bread.</description><price>9.0</price></item><item id="4"><name>Yangchou Fried Rice</name><description>Fluffy steamed rice stir-fried with eggs, fresh vegetables and diced chicken in a wok.</description><price>9.95</price></item><item id="5"><name>Southern Fried Chicken</name><description>Breaded chicken, flovoured with a Southern blend of spices, fried to succulent crispness.</description><price>10.5</price></item><item id="6"><name>Spaghetti Alle Vongole</name><description>Freshly made pasta dough doused with a flavourful reduction from white wine and Manila clams.</description><price>14.6</price></item><item id="7"><name>Tom Yum Goong</name><description>Fragrant seafood broth served with a plate of Jasmine rice from the doorsteps of Thailand. Note: Spicy</description><price>12.8</price></item><item id="8"><name>Coke</name><description>A tall glass of ice cold Coke.</description><price>3.0</price></item><item id="9"><name>Hot Earl Grey Tea</name><description>A freshly brewed beverage using the hand-picked tea leaves from Ceylon.</description><price>5.0</price></item><item id="10"><name>Lychee Smoothie</name><description>Straight from the orchard into the glass, this heavenly concoction will definitely please your tastebuds.</description><price>3.0</price></item><item id="11"><name>Salted Egg Souffle</name><description>Delightful salted egg infused in a perfectly baked souffle.</description><price>13.5</price></item><item id="12"><name>Peach Cobbler</name><description>With the heavenly Artic Supreme peach as a filling, this delicious dessert is baked daily to ensure freshness.</description><price>7.9</price></item><item id="13"><name>Apple pie</name><description>Juicy pie of apple</description><price>3.0</price></item></Root>